# N. NANDINEE

Date of Birth: December 6, 1999 | Age: 24 | Gender: Female

Address: Metro View Apartments, Flat 75, Sector 13, Pocket B, Phase 2, Dwarka, New Delhi (110078) Contact No: +91-8178934329 | Email: narayan.nandinee@gmail.com | Portfolio: Link to Work Samples

#### **Profile**

With a two-year editorial background, I'm a former junior content writer with a sharp eye for detail, excellent grammar, proofreading, editing, and a knack for creating plagiarism-free content through research. I'm currently looking for new opportunities to improve my abilities and broaden my knowledge within the industry. I'm willing to accept worthwhile positions for your esteemed organization and use my skills from my bachelor's degree, which also covers a variety of industries including copywriting, public relations, graphic designing, advertising, and more.

#### Education

#### Bachelor of Arts, Journalism & Mass Communications

2021

University: Amity School Of Communication – Noida, Uttar Pradesh

- First Division with Distinction
- 8.99/10 CGPA
- Received 30% academic merit-based scholarship during the program

## Senior School Certification , Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE)

2018

School: B.G.S International Public School – New Delhi

- Field of Study: Commerce with Mathematics
- 6.69/10 CGPA

#### Secondary School Certification, Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE)

2016

School: B.G.S International Public School - New Delhi

• 8.8/10 CGPA

## Experience

#### Junior Content Writer (Editorial) | Link to Profile

Mar 2022 to Aug 2024

Company: Web News Observer, Stacknexo LLP – Mysore, Karnataka

- Generated six complete articles on a daily basis
- · Verifying information and story details
- Ensure accuracy and plagiarism detection
- Ensured consistent formatting of publications

#### Content Writer | Link to Certificate

Company: Holla Digital - New Delhi

Created strategic content based on keyword planning

- Utilizes exceptional writing and editing skills
- Complete three to four assignments on a daily basis
- Produced error-free and engaging content by proofreading

Aug 2020 to Oct 2020

#### Human Resources (HR) | Link to Certificate

Company: Youth Empowerment Foundation – New Delhi

- Implemented seminar schedules on a weekly basis
- Consistently delivered projects ahead of schedule
- Supervised a team of employees
- Managed the candidate's hiring process

#### Social Media Marketing | Link to Certificate

Company: Success Foundation - New Delhi

- Created graphic designs to enhance ad campaigns
- Developed video content for social media
- Creating blog posts and content for social media
- Created powerpoint presentations

#### Fundraising | Link to Certificate

Company: Youth Empowerment Foundation – New Delhi

- Composed grant proposals and fundraising newsletter
- Planned successful fundraising events
- Managed and orchestrated donation campaigns
- Create awareness about fundraising campaigns

### Media And Public Relations | Link to Certificate

Company: Picartzo Services Ltd. – New Delhi

- Oversaw candidate selection
- · Played an active role in team-building initiatives
- Generated leads for company's influencer engagement
- Content creation and distribution

#### Skills

- Computer Proficiency
- Content Management System
- Canva
- Adobe Creative Suite

- Keyword Planning and SEO
- Ms-Office
- Wordpress
- Google Analytics

#### Certifications

- Business Communications Certification Amity Institute of English Studies & Research
- Foreign Language Certification (Spanish) Amity School of Foreign Languages
- Behavioural Science Certification Amity Center of Behavioral Science
- Digital Marketing Internshala Trainings
- Creative Writing Internshala Trainings

### **Projects**

#### Research Paper

- Publication: TRANS-Asian Journal Of Marketing And Management Research (Volume 10)
- Issue: Sept-Oct 2021, ISSN: 2279-0667, DOI Number: 10.5958/2279-0667.2021.00040.7
- Subject: Media Transition A Study On The Impact Of Digital Platforms On News And Journalistic Content In India. (Link | Page No. 4-27)

#### **Documentary**

 Contributed as script writer and producer for a mini documentary titled, "Kulhad: A Mini Documentary On Pottery." (<u>Link | YouTube</u>)

Sept 2020 to Sept 2020

Sept 2020 to Nov 2020

Jul 2020 to Aug 2020

May 2020 to Jun 2020